Daniel Geddes

Software Engineer

Profile

Motivated professional looking to pursue a career change into the technology industry for a company with long term prospects.

I have over 800 hours of course time on Codecademy and can provide certificates of completion of the technologies listed upon request.

Technical Skills

Front-end Web Languages/ Frameworks (installation, configuration and use)

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript(ES6), React, jQuery.

Back-end Web Languages/ Frameworks (installation, configuration and use)

Node.js and NPM, Express.js

Database Technologies (installation, configuration and use)

SQL, SQLITE3, MongoDB

Other Technologies (installation, configuration and use)

PHP, C#, Java, Python

Git, Bash

Microsoft Office, Open Office.

Test Driven Development

Mocha and Chai

Hardware and Software (installation, configuration and use)

Employment History

Carpentry Supervisor at SC4 Carpentry LTD, Portsmouth

July 2019 — April 2020

Building high quality timber frame products which included timber frame packages, hand cut and trussed roofs, first fixing (all in accordance with HSE guidelines) on building sites in Southampton/Eastleigh. Read technical drawings and offered revisions. Excellent health and safety knowledge and repeated practice. Attention to detail was essential.

Carpentry Supervisor at AGB Carpentry LTD, Portsmouth

September 2014 — July 2019

Acted as first point of contact with site managers whilst also delivering high quality timber frame packages, hand cut and trussed roofs. Responsibilities included supplying fixings, giving toolbox talks/training, setting up cranes and liaising with site team while also ensuring targets were met. I trained new apprentices. Emailed status and completion forms for managers as well as writing risk assessment and method statements.

Details

07568523047

dangeddes22@gmail.com

Links

Portfolio Github

Skills

Excellent written and verbal communication.

Self-motivated home learner.

Logical thinker.

Excellent attendance record.

Enthusiastic hard worker.

Stockroom Supervisor at Primark, Portsmouth

August 2012 — August 2014

Telephonist at AquaCars LTD, Portsmouth

November 2011 — August 2012

Window Cleaner at Hi-Flo H20 LTD, Portsmouth

May 2011 — November 2011

Education

Electrical Installation, Highbury College, Portsmouth

September 2013 — July 2014

Level 2

Hospitality and Catering, Highbury College, Portsmouth

September 2010 — July 2011

Level 2

GCSE's, Miltoncross School, Portsmouth

October 2020 — October 2020

10 GCSE's A-C including Maths English, IT and Science.